<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>VideoInsights</title>
    <link>https://zain6khan.github.io/video-insights-landing-page/</link>
    <description>Recent content on VideoInsights</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Zain Khan</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 14 May 2024 17:39:55 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://zain6khan.github.io/video-insights-landing-page/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Getting Started with VideoInsights</title>
      <link>https://zain6khan.github.io/video-insights-landing-page/post/first-post/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2024 10:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>https://zain6khan.github.io/video-insights-landing-page/post/first-post/</guid>
      <description>Getting Started with VideoInsights Welcome to your first post about VideoInsights. In this post, we&amp;rsquo;ll explore how you can enhance your learning experience with the VideoInsights Chrome extension.&#xA;What is VideoInsights? VideoInsights is a Chrome extension designed to revolutionize your learning experience by providing curated video results, personalized learning recommendations, and seamless integration with your web browsing. Whether you are a student, educator, or lifelong learner, VideoInsights helps you find relevant educational videos quickly and easily.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://zain6khan.github.io/video-insights-landing-page/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://zain6khan.github.io/video-insights-landing-page/about/</guid>
      <description>About Us Made with ❤️ by the Hugo Bootstrap Theme team.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Code of Conduct</title>
      <link>https://zain6khan.github.io/video-insights-landing-page/code-of-conduct/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://zain6khan.github.io/video-insights-landing-page/code-of-conduct/</guid>
      <description>Contributor Covenant Code of Conduct Our Pledge We as members, contributors, and leaders pledge to make participation in our community a harassment-free experience for everyone, regardless of age, body size, visible or invisible disability, ethnicity, sex characteristics, gender identity and expression, level of experience, education, socio-economic status, nationality, personal appearance, race, caste, color, religion, or sexual identity and orientation.&#xA;We pledge to act and interact in ways that contribute to an open, welcoming, diverse, inclusive, and healthy community.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>https://zain6khan.github.io/video-insights-landing-page/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://zain6khan.github.io/video-insights-landing-page/contact/</guid>
      <description>Contact Open an issue on GitHub.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Privacy Policy</title>
      <link>https://zain6khan.github.io/video-insights-landing-page/privacy-policy/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://zain6khan.github.io/video-insights-landing-page/privacy-policy/</guid>
      <description>Privacy Policy TLDR: We do not use cookies and we do not collect any personal data.&#xA;Website visitors No personal information is collected. No information is stored in the browser. No information is shared with, sent to or sold to third-parties. No information is shared with advertising companies. No information is mined and harvested for personal and behavioral trends. No information is monetized. Information we collect and what we use it for The server hosting this site can collect the following information:</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VideoInsights Overview 🎥📚</title>
      <link>https://zain6khan.github.io/video-insights-landing-page/page/fitness_page/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://zain6khan.github.io/video-insights-landing-page/page/fitness_page/</guid>
      <description>VideoInsights Overview VideoInsights is designed to revolutionize your learning experience. By leveraging state-of-the-art AI technology, VideoInsights offers curated video results, personalized learning recommendations, and a seamless integration with your web browsing. Explore the extension&amp;rsquo;s capabilities and get ready to enhance your knowledge efficiently.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
